Welcome to the new feature introduction video of Marvelous Designer 2024.
In this video, we will introduce you to the new feature of multiple wind control.
This feature will allow you to create a more diversified effect when you simulate blowing wind.
Now we have a project file of the jellyfish.
You can see that it has been simulated and recorded.
In the animation recorded for the first time, we did not activate the blowing effect.
Now let's add some and record the animation again.
Open the wind control device.
We will use the wind control device to produce some water flow effects.
We will create a total of four wind control devices.
First, create a wind control device that blows in the horizontal direction of the water.
Rotate it to the blowing arrow to match the water.
Then click on the fire image to activate the blowing effect.
We set the strength of this wind control device to 80 and the air flow to 20.
The higher the strength, the stronger the blowing.
The higher the air flow, the more irregular the blowing.
Then select this wind control device.
In the menu bar on the right, select copy.
Copy a wind control device.
Place the copied wind control device on the other side of the water.
Rotate the blowing arrow to match the water.
In the menu bar on the right of the wind control device,
you can choose to copy, activate, activate, or delete the wind control device.
We set the strength of the wind control device to 70 and the air flow to 30.
Then continue to create two wind control devices that blow up and down.
Copy the wind control device and rotate it until the blowing arrow heads up.
Increase its strength to 100 and the air flow to 35.
Then create a wind control device that blows down.
This wind control device has a stronger attribute than the wind control device that blows up.
In this way, we can create a wind that blows up and down.
Through these blowing effects, we simulate the floating effect of the water in the water.
Select the wind control device that blows down.
Set its strength to 150 and the air flow to 60.
The wind in this direction is the strongest.
Next, let's record the animation after the blowing effect is turned on.
Through multiple wind control devices, you can achieve a more diversified simulation effect.
You can set different blowing directions for these wind control devices,
different numbers to achieve a more real blowing effect or create a special animation effect.
In addition, we would like to introduce to you
the setting of the wireless border.
This setting is turned on in default state.
The wind control device that is connected to this option
will blow up in the whole space of the five borders.
If you cancel the connection of this option,
the blowing of the wind control device will only work within the specified range.
At the same time, the wind control device will show the frame of the blowing border around it.
In this example, you can see
the significant difference in the blowing effect after closing the wireless border.
After closing the wireless border,
you can adjust the position of the wind control device
or the wind control device rotation to adjust the blowing effect through the location ball.
In addition,
you can set the position of the wind control device
In addition, click the search icon on the upper right of the locator to enter the search mode.
At this time, drag the axis of the locator to adjust the blowing range of the wind control.
After adjustment, look at the simulation, you will see the changes in the blowing effect.
Let's try it.